https://www.logoworks.com/privacy-policy/

LOGOWORKS PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy informs you of LogoWorks’ privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way we collect and use your information. LogoWorks is sometimes referred to using the terms “us”, “we”, “our” and similar terms.
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to all websites, domains, services, applications, and products owned or operated by us or our wholly owned subsidiaries, including those “powered by” another company on our behalf (each, a “Service”), except that a privacy policy or statement that applies to a particular Service may supersede or supplement this privacy policy.
Our Services may provide links to third-party applications, products, services, or websites. If you access those links, you will leave our site and will be beyond the coverage of this privacy policy. We do not control those third party sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from our practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party sites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by this privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any site you interact with before allowing the collection and use of your personal information.
We may also provide social media features that enable you to share information with your social networks and to interact with our Services on various social media sites. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings on the social media sites with which you interact to make sure you understand the information that may be collected, used, and shared by those sites.
Collection of Personal Information
We collect, export, and use your personal information to better serve you and personalize your experience and interaction with our Services. By using our services, you consent to our collecting, exporting and using your personal information in the manner described in this privacy policy.
We may collect personal information from you to complete various transactions, such as:
Contact information, such as your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address;
Financial information, such as your credit card number; and
Other unique information, such as user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, product and service preferences, contact preferences, educational and employment background, and job interest data.
If you choose to use a referral program on our site, we will ask you for your referral’s e-mail address, mobile phone number, or other contact information and automatically send your referral a one-time message inviting your referral to visit the site. We use and store this information only for the purpose of sending this one-time referral message.
If you post, comment, indicate interest, or share personal information, including photographs, to any public forum on one of our sites, social networks, blogs, or similar forums, any personal information you submit can be read, viewed, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to contact you or for purposes that neither you nor we have control over. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums.
In addition to the information you provide, we also may collect information during your use of our Services, through tools, which include Web beacons, cookies, and embedded Web links. These tools collect certain traffic information that your browser sends to a website, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, unique device identifier, clickstream behavior (for example, the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with our Services) and product information. We may also use some of these tools in connection with certain e-mails and communications sent by us or on our behalf and by doing this we may collect information using these tools when you open the e-mail or click on a link contained in the e-mail.
We use remarketing campaigns with Google to advertise our services online. In conjunction with these services, a cookie is placed on your computer that indicates you have visited the Logoworks site. Google will use this cookie to show you ads on sites across the internet. You can opt-out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads settings.
We also collect information from commercially available sources that we deem credible. This information may include your name, address, e-mail address, preferences, interests, and demographic/profile data. The information we collect from commercial sources may be used along with the information we collect when you use our Services. For example, we may compare the geographic information acquired from commercial sources with your IP address to determine your general geographic area.
How We Use Your Information
Respond to duly authorized information requests of police and governmental authorities;
Comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order;
Investigate and help prevent security threats, fraud or other malicious activity;
Enforce or protect our rights and properties; or
Protect the rights or personal safety of our employees and third parties on or using our Services.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its Services to children under 13. We encourage parents and other care givers to take appropriate steps to monitor online activities and interests and prevent them from using services that are inappropriate for them.
Your Choices and Selecting Your Privacy Preferences
We give you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our Services. You can subscribe to receive certain information related to specific Services and also choose to receive general communications from us by mail, e-mail, telephone or mobile device. Some communications may utilize automatic data collection tools.
Access to and Accuracy of Your Information
We strive to maintain your personal information accurately. We allow you to access your personal information to review and correct it or ask for anonymization, blockage, or deletion, as applicable. To protect your privacy and security, we may also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.
Keeping Your Personal Information Secure
We take reasonable and appropriate physical, technical, and administrative precautions to safeguard the information we collect, prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of the information. We retain data only as required or permitted by applicable law.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
If we modify this privacy policy, we will post the revised statement here, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our statement, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an e-mail or posting a notice on our website and/or social media pages.
Contacting Us
If you have comments or questions about this privacy policy, please send them to support@logoworks.com:
We Are Open For Business!
Call Us: (919) 244.2535Send an emailFacebookInstagramLinkedInTwitter
